<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RMS_FinalExer1</string>

    <string-array name="productNames">
        <item>CEO Latté</item>
        <item>Buttercrème Latté</item>
        <item>Spanish Latté</item>
        <item>Gula Melaka</item>
        <item>Seasalt Brown Sugar</item>
        <item>Australian Chocolate</item>
        <item>Salted Caramel</item>
        <item>Matcha Craze</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="productPrices">
        <item>95.00</item>
        <item>120.00</item>
        <item>95.00</item>
        <item>95.00</item>
        <item>130.00</item>
        <item>115.00</item>
        <item>155.00</item>
        <item>155.00</item>

    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="productImages">
        <item>@drawable/ceolatte</item>
        <item>@drawable/buttercremelatte</item>
        <item>@drawable/spanishlatte</item>
        <item>@drawable/gulamelaka</item>
        <item>@drawable/seasaltbrownsugar</item>
        <item>@drawable/australianchoco</item>
        <item>@drawable/saltedcaramel</item>
        <item>@drawable/matchacraze</item>

    </integer-array>

    <string name="ceoLatte">
        Bold, aromatic, and made for leaders. The CEO Latté combines our signature strong brew with a smooth finish — designed to boost your drive with every sip.
    </string>

    <string name="bcLatte">
        Treat yourself to a rich, buttery infusion paired with smooth espresso and velvety milk, finished with a sweet buttercrème swirl. Ideal for those who savor comfort in every cup.
    </string>

    <string name="spanishLatte">
        A sweet, creamy blend where bold espresso meets a trio of rich milks. This smooth classic delivers a warm, full-bodied flavor that’s hard to resist.
    </string>

    <string name="gulaMelaka">
        Taste the tropics with our iced Gula Melaka latté — a fusion of deep muscovado-style syrup and subtle coconut notes. Refreshing and uniquely satisfying.
    </string>

    <string name="ssbSugar">
        A sweet-savory twist combining rich brown sugar and Gula Melaka syrup with a hint of sea salt cream, topped off with espresso for a bold yet smooth finish.
    </string>

    <string name="ausChoco">
        Dive into creamy indulgence with our Australian Chocolate blend — a harmonious mix of rich cocoa and smooth milk for a perfectly balanced chocolate treat.
    </string>

    <string name="saltedCaramel">
        A sweet-and-salty delight with a velvety caramel flavor and just the right hint of salt. Blended to icy perfection for fans of a timeless favorite.
    </string>

    <string name="matchaCraze">
        Chill with this refreshing frappé, made from authentic Japanese Matcha and crowned with a swirl of whipped cream — an energizing green tea escape.
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="cart_list">Shopping cart items</string>
</resources>